Welcome back to my series where I
recreate Ben & Jerry's flavors, but
lower in calories and higher in protein.
This is pistachio pistachio. Let me show
you how to make it. And no, we're not
using that sugarfree Jell-O pistachio
pudding mix. If you think that tastes
like pistachio, your taste buds are even
more cooked than mine, and that's saying
a lot. Instead, we're using pistachio
butter or pistachio cream, whichever one
you can find, and then a little bit of
sugar-free pistachio syrup. You really
don't want to use a lot of this cuz it
can be very artificial and it can ruin
the flavor. So, just a splash. If you
don't have it, totally fine. The flavor
is going to be very similar. But trust
me, this pistachio flavor is so so much
closer to real pistachio ice cream. It
honestly brought me back to Italy. And I
know that's insane to say given that
this is a third of the calories and
probably double the protein, but I am so
serious when I say that. To complete
this Ben & Jerry's flavor, we're going
to add in some lightly roasted salted
pistachios and run it on the mixing
setting. And boom. That is the best
protein pistachio ice cream you will
try.